Guide to the Washington Theater Club records, 1952-1983 MS2061
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- General Accounting, 1957-1974; MS2061 Series 3
  - Expenditures Washington Drama Center Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1957-1963 (Box 160, Folder 1762)
  - Expenditures Washington Drama Center Production & Office, 1957-1963 (Box 160, Folder 1763)
  - Expenditures Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1958-1959 (Box 160, Folder 1764)
  - Expenditures Production & Office, 1958-1959 (Box 160, Folder 1765)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1958-1959 (Box 161, Folder 1766)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1959-1960 (Box 161, Folder 1767)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, 1959-1960 (Box 161, Folder 1768)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1959-1960 (Box 161, Folder 1769)
  - Expenditures, Box Office, 1959-1960 (Box 161, Folder 1770)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Matchmaker, 1959-1960 (Box 161, Folder 1771)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - A Hatful of Rain, 1959-1960 (Box 161, Folder 1772)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Lesson & The Chairs, 1959-1960 (Box 161, Folder 1773)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - A Clearing in the Woods, 1959-1960 (Box 161, Folder 1774)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1960-1961 (Box 161, Folder 1775)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, 1960-1961 (Box 161, Folder 1776)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1960-1961 (Box 161, Folder 1777)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1961-1962 (Box 161, Folder 1778)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office 1, 1961-1962 (Box 162, Folder 1779)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office 2, 1961-1962 (Box 162, Folder 1780)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1961-1962 (Box 162, Folder 1781)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1962-1963 (Box 162, Folder 1782)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, 1962-1963 (Box 163, Folder 1783)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1962-1963 (Box 163, Folder 1784)
  - Expenditures, Box Office, 1962-1963 (Box 163, Folder 1785)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Establishment, 1962-1963 (Box 163, Folder 1786)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Brecht on Brecht, 1962-1963 (Box 163, Folder 1787)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Winter Peach, 1962-1963 (Box 163, Folder 1788)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 1789)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office 1, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 1790)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office 2, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 1791)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 1792)
  - Expenditures, Box Office, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 1793)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Children's Theater - The Emperor's New Clothes, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 1794)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Non-Equity - Amurica, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 1795)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Children's Theater - Beauty and the Beast, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 1796)
  - Expenditures, Company Box Office - Dance - Virginia Freeman & the Dance Repertory, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 1797)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Showcase Production, 1963-1964 (Box 164, Folder 1798)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Non-Equity - Zoo Story & The Sandbox, 1963-1964 (Box 165, Folder 1799)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Non-Equity - Waiting for Godot, 1963-1964 (Box 165, Folder 1800)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Non-Equity - Ondine, 1963-1964 (Box 165, Folder 1801)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Summer Festival, 1963-1964 (Box 165, Folder 1802)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Non-Equity - Dumbwaiter & The Collection, 1963-1964 (Box 165, Folder 1803)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1964-1965 (Box 165, Folder 1804)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office 1, 1964-1965 (Box 165, Folder 1805)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office 2, 1964-1965 (Box 165, Folder 1806)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1964-1965 (Box 165, Folder 1807)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Non-Equity - The Death of Bessie Smith & Play, 1964-1965 (Box 165, Folder 1808)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Non-Equity - 2x2, 1964-1965 (Box 165, Folder 1809)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1965-1966 (Box 165, Folder 1810)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, 1965-1966 (Box 165, Folder 1811)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1965-1966 (Box 166, Folder 1812)
  - Expenditures, Box Office, 1965-1966 (Box 166, Folder 1813)
  - Expenditures, Box Office- The Typists & The Tiger, 1965-1966 (Box 166, Folder 1814)
  - Expenditures, Box Office- Birthday Party, 1965-1966 (Box 166, Folder 1815)
  - Expenditures, Box Office- Concerts - Songs of Yesterday, 1965-1966 (Box 166, Folder 1816)
  - Expenditures, Box Office- Eccentricities of a Nightingale, 1965-1966 (Box 166, Folder 1817)
  - Expenditures, Box Office- Spread Eagle, 1965-1966 (Box 166, Folder 1818)
  - Expenditures, Box Office- Special Events - An Evening with Sue and Pugh, 1965-1966 (Box 166, Folder 1819)
  - Expenditures, Box Office- Children's Theater - Lady Precious Stream, 1965-1966 (Box 166, Folder 1820)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1966-1967 (Box 166, Folder 1821)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, Oct.-Feb., 1966-1967 (Box 167, Folder 1822)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, March 1967, 1966-1967 (Box 167, Folder 1823)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, Apr. 1967, 1966-1967 (Box 168, Folder 1824)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, May-Sept. 1967, 1966-1967 (Box 168, Folder 1825)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1966-1967 (Box 169, Folder 1826)
  - Expenditures, Box Office, 1966-1967 (Box 169, Folder 1827)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Knack Oct. 13-Nov. 6, 1966-1967 (Box 169, Folder 1828)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Lover & Hughie Nov. 10-Dec. 4, 1966-1967 (Box 169, Folder 1829)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Fantastics Dec. 8-Jan. 15, 1966-1967 (Box 169, Folder 1830)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Tiny Alice Jan. 19-Feb. 12, 1966-1967 (Box 169, Folder 1831)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Marriage of Mr. Mississippi Feb. 16-Mar. 12, 1966-1967 (Box 170, Folder 1832)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Killer Mar. 16-Apr. 9, 1966-1967 (Box 170, Folder 1833)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Waters of Babylon Apr. 13-May 7, 1966-1967 (Box 170, Folder 1834)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Son of Spread Eagle May 11-July 25, 1966-1967 (Box 170, Folder 1835)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Children's Theater - The Breman Town Musicians June 4-Sept. 2, 1966-1967 (Box 170, Folder 1836)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Luv July 28-Aug. 28, 1966-1967 (Box 170, Folder 1837)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1967-1968 (Box 170, Folder 1838)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office 1, 1967-1968 (Box 170, Folder 1839)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office 2, 1967-1968 (Box 171, Folder 1840)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1967-1968 (Box 171, Folder 1841)
  - Expenditures, Box Office, 1967-1968 (Box 171, Folder 1842)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - My Sweet Charlie Oct. 12-Nov. 19, 1967-1968 (Box 171, Folder 1843)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Five Evenings, 1967-1968 (Box 171, Folder 1844)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Green Julia & The Basement.May 9 - June 16, 1967-1968 (Box 171, Folder 1845)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1968-1969 (Box 171, Folder 1846)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office 1, 1968-1969 (Box 171, Folder 1847)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office 2, 1968-1969 (Box 171, Folder 1848)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1968-1969 (Box 172, Folder 1849)
  - Expenditures, Box Office, 1968-1969 (Box 172, Folder 1850)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Gingham Dog, 1968 September 26-October 27 (Box 172, Folder 1851)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Lion in Winter Oct. 31-Dec. 1, 1968-1969 (Box 172, Folder 1852)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Lock Up Your Daughters Dec. 5-Jan. 5, 1968-1969 (Box 172, Folder 1853)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Mr. Tambo, Mr. Bones Jan. 9-Feb. 9, 1968-1969 (Box 172, Folder 1854)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Who's Happpy Now? Feb. 13-Mar. 16, 1968-1969 (Box 172, Folder 1855)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Indian Wants the Bronx Mar. 20-Apr. 20, 1968-1969 (Box 172, Folder 1856)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Bread and Butter Apr. 24-May 25, 1968-1969 (Box 172, Folder 1857)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Spread Eagle IV June 4-Aug. 10, 1968-1969 (Box 172, Folder 1858)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1969-1970 (Box 173, Folder 1859)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, 1969-1970 (Box 173, Folder 1860)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1969-1970 (Box 173, Folder 1861)
  - Expenditures, Subscriptions, 1969-1970 (Box 173, Folder 1862)
  - Expenditures, Box Office, 1969-1970 (Box 173, Folder 1863)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Moths, 1969-1970 (Box 173, Folder 1864)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Decline and Fall of the Entire World as Seen through the Eyes of Cole Porter Dec. 10-Apr. 12, 1969-1970 (Box 173, Folder 1865)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Wolves, 1969-1970 (Box 173, Folder 1866)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Adventures in the Skin Trade Feb. 25-Mar. 22, 1969-1970 (Box 173, Folder 1867)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Serenading Louie Apr. 1-26, 1969-1970 (Box 173, Folder 1868)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Continental Divide Apr. 29-May 31, 1969-1970 (Box 174, Folder 1869)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Exit the King June 10-July 5, 1969-1970 (Box 174, Folder 1870)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Before You Go July 15-Aug. 16, 1969-1970 (Box 174, Folder 1871)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1970-1971 (Box 174, Folder 1872)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, 1970-1971 (Box 174, Folder 1873)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office - Monday Night Staged Readings, 1970-1971 (Box 174, Folder 1874)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1970-1971 (Box 174, Folder 1875)
  - Expenditures, Subscriptions, 1970-1971 (Box 174, Folder 1876)
  - Expenditures, Box Office, 1970-1971 (Box 174, Folder 1877)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Effect of Gamma Rays on Man-in-the-Moon Marigolds Sept. 23-Nov. 1, 1970-1971 (Box 175, Folder 1878)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Last Sweet Days of Isaac Nov. 11-Dec. 6, 1970-1971 (Box 175, Folder 1879)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - A Fifth of Spread Eagle Dec. 16-Jan. 10, 1970-1971 (Box 175, Folder 1880)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Little Boxes, 1970-1971 (Box 175, Folder 1881)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Web and the Rock, 1970-1971 (Box 175, Folder 1882)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Chinese & Dr. Fish, 1970-1971 (Box 175, Folder 1883)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Father's Day, 1970-1971 (Box 175, Folder 1884)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Whores, Wars, and Tin Pan Alley, 1970-1971 (Box 175, Folder 1885)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1971-1972 (Box 175, Folder 1886)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, Sept.-Oct.1971, 1971-1972 (Box 176, Folder 1887)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, Nov.-Dec.1971, 1971-1972 (Box 176, Folder 1888)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, Jan.-Feb.1972, 1971-1972 (Box 176, Folder 1889)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, Mar.-Apr.1972, 1971-1972 (Box 176, Folder 1890)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, May-Aug., 1971-1972 (Box 177, Folder 1891)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1971-1972 (Box 177, Folder 1892)
  - Expenditures, Subscriptions, 1971-1972 (Box 177, Folder 1893)
  - Expenditures, Box Office, 1971-1972 (Box 178, Folder 1894)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Adaptation/Next, 1971-1972 (Box 178, Folder 1895)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - All Over, 1971-1972 (Box 178, Folder 1896)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Curse You, Spread Eagle 1 - advance sale - Dec. 13, 1971-1972 (Box 179, Folder 1897)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Curse You, Spread Eagle 2. Dec. 14-Jan. 9, 1971-1972 (Box 179, Folder 1898)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Lemon Sky, 1971-1972 (Box 180, Folder 1899)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Philanthropist. Feb. 16-Mar. 12, 1971-1972 (Box 180, Folder 1900)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Washington Square, 1971-1972 (Box 180, Folder 1901)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Four Minus One Apr. 26-May 21, 1971-1972 (Box 181, Folder 1902)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Lady Audley's Secret. May 31-July 16, 1971-1972 (Box 181, Folder 1903)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1972-1973 (Box 182, Folder 1904)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, Sept.-Nov.1972 1, 1972-1973 (Box 182, Folder 1905)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, Sept.-Nov.1972, 1972-1973 (Box 182, Folder 1906)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, Dec.-Feb. 1972/73, 1972-1973 (Box 183, Folder 1907)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, Mar.-Apr, 1972-1973 (Box 184, Folder 1908)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, May-Aug., 1972-1973 (Box 184, Folder 1909)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1972-1973 (Box 185, Folder 1910)
  - Expenditures, Subscriptions, 1972-1973 (Box 185, Folder 1911)
  - Expenditures, Box Office, 1972-1973 (Box 185, Folder 1912)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Spread Eagle Papers, Sept. 27-Oct. 29 1, 1972-1973 (Box 185, Folder 1913)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Spread Eagle Papers Sept. 27-Oct. 29 2, 1972-1973 (Box 186, Folder 1914)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Rapists Nov. 9-Dec. 6, 1972-1973 (Box 186, Folder 1915)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Boys from Syracuse Dec. 13-Jan. 7, 1972-1973 (Box 186, Folder 1916)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Children's Theater - Holiday on Strings Dec. 22-29, 1972-1973 (Box 187, Folder 1917)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Ceremonies in Dark Old Men, Mar. 6-Apr. 10 1, 1972-1973 (Box 187, Folder 1918)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Ceremonies in Dark Old Men, Mar. 6-Apr. 10 2, 1972-1973 (Box 187, Folder 1919)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Enclave Feb. 12-Mar. 18 1, 1972-1973 (Box 188, Folder 1920)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Enclave Feb. 12-Mar. 18 2, 1972-1973 (Box 188, Folder 1921)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Scenes from American Life Mar. 28-Apr. 22, 1972-1973 (Box 188, Folder 1922)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Children's Theater - Rumple 1972 -1973, 1973 April 14-21 (Box 189, Folder 1923)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - The Ecstasy of Rita Joe May 2-27, 1972-1973 (Box 189, Folder 1924)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Something Wild June 6-July 1, 1972-1973 (Box 189, Folder 1925)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Inner City 07/18/1973-12/23/1973; 07/11/1974-04/04/1974, 1973-1974 (Box 190, Folder 1926)
  - Expenditures, Building Supplies & Maintenance, 1973-1974 (Box 190, Folder 1927)
  - Expenditures, Production & Office, 1973-1974 (Box 190, Folder 1928)
  - Expenditures, Promotion, 1973-1974 (Box 190, Folder 1929)
  - Expenditures, Box Office, 1973-1974 (Box 190, Folder 1930)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - A Difficult Borning, 1973 November 15-25 (Box 190, Folder 1931)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Thoughts Jan. 23-Feb. 17, 1973-1974 (Box 190, Folder 1932)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Behind the Broken Words Mar. 8-24, 1973-1974 (Box 190, Folder 1933)
  - Expenditures, Box Office - Children's Theater - The ABC's, 1974 June 19-April 04 (Box 190, Folder 1934)
  - Insurance, Workmen's Compensation, undated (Box 191, Folder 1935)
  - Insurance, Fire & Liability, undated (Box 191, Folder 1936)
  - Insurance, Group Health, undated (Box 191, Folder 1937)
  - Insurance, Automobile, undated (Box 191, Folder 1938)
  - Insurance, Fidelity Bonds, 1970-1972 (Box 191, Folder 1939)
  - Bank Checks, National Bank of Washington, Washington Theater Club, 1957-1958 (Box 192, Folder 1940)
  - Bank Checks, National Bank of Washington, Washington Drama Center, 1958-1959 (Box 192, Folder 1941)
  - Bank Checks, National Bank of Washington, Washington Theater Club, 1959 (Box 192, Folder 1942)
  - Bank Checks, National Bank of Washington, Washington Theater Club, 1960 (Box 192, Folder 1943)
  - Bank Checks, National Bank of Washington, Washington Drama Center, 1960 (Box 192, Folder 1944)
  - Bank Checks, National Bank of Washington, Washington Theater Club, 1961 (Box 192, Folder 1945)
  - Bank Checks, National Bank of Washington, Washington Theater Club, 1962 (Box 193, Folder 1946)
  - Bank Checks, National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, Washington Theater Club, 1963 (Box 193, Folder 1948)
  - Bank Checks, National Bank of Washington, 048 96 1, Washington Drama Center, 1963 (Box 194, Folder 1949)
  - Bank Checks, National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, Washington Theater Club, 1964 (Box 194, Folder 1950)
  - Bank Checks, National Bank of Washington, Washington Drama Center, 1964 (Box 194, Folder 1951)
  - Bank Checks, National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, Washington Theater Club, 1965 (Box 194, Folder 1952)
  - Bank Checks, National Bank of Washington, 3 657 43 4, Special, 1965-1966 (Box 194, Folder 1953)
  - Bank Checks, National Bank of Washington, 3 735 10 9, Subscriptions, 1966 (Box 194, Folder 1954)
  - Bank Checks, May-Oct., National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, 1967 (Box 195, Folder 1955)
  - Bank Checks, Nov.-Dec., National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, 1967 (Box 195, Folder 1956)
  - Bank Checks, May-July, Union Trust, 3 059 502, Benefit Account, 1968 (Box 195, Folder 1957)
  - Bank Checks, Sept.-Nov., National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, 1968 (Box 196, Folder 1958)
  - Bank Checks, Oct.-Dec., Union Trust, 3057 860, Payroll, 1968 (Box 196, Folder 1959)
  - Bank Checks, Jan., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1969 (Box 196, Folder 1960)
  - Bank Checks, Jan.-Feb., National Bank: of Washington, 048 44 9, 1969 (Box 196, Folder 1961)
  - Bank Checks, Feb., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1969 (Box 197, Folder 1962)
  - Bank Checks, Mar., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1969 (Box 197, Folder 1963)
  - Bank Checks, Mar.-May, National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, 1969 (Box 197, Folder 1964)
  - Bank Checks, Apr., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1969 (Box 197, Folder 1965)
  - Bank Checks, May, Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1969 (Box 198, Folder 1966)
  - Bank Checks, June, Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1969 (Box 198, Folder 1967)
  - Bank Checks, June-July, National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, 1969 (Box 198, Folder 1968)
  - Bank Checks, June-Nov., District of Columbia National Bank, 240 354 8, Children's Theater, 1969 (Box 198, Folder 1969)
  - Bank Checks, June-Dec. First National Bank of Washington, 024 832 0, Capital Fund Drive, 1969-1972 (Box 198, Folder 1970)
  - Bank Checks, July, Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1969 (Box 199, Folder 1971)
  - Bank Checks, Aug., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1969 (Box 199, Folder 1972)
  - Bank Checks, Aug.-Sept., National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, 1969 (Box 199, Folder 1973)
  - Bank Checks, Sept., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1969 (Box 199, Folder 1974)
  - Bank Checks, Oct., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1969 (Box 200, Folder 1975)
  - Bank Checks, Oct.-Dec., National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, 1969 (Box 200, Folder 1976)
  - Bank Checks, Nov., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1969 (Box 200, Folder 1977)
  - Bank Checks, Dec., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1969 (Box 200, Folder 1978)
  - Bank Checks, Bank Checks, Jan., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1970 (Box 201, Folder 1979)
  - Bank Checks, Jan., National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, 1970 (Box 201, Folder 1980)
  - Bank Checks, Feb., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1970 (Box 201, Folder 1981)
  - Bank Checks, Mar., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Paryoll, 1970 (Box 201, Folder 1982)
  - Bank Checks, Apr., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1970 (Box 202, Folder 1983)
  - Bank Checks, May, Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1970 (Box 202, Folder 1984)
  - Bank Checks, May-Sept., First National Bank of Washington, 025256 5, subscriptions, 1970 (Box 202, Folder 1985)
  - Bank Checks, June, Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1970 (Box 202, Folder 1986)
  - Bank Checks, July, Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1970 (Box 203, Folder 1987)
  - Bank Checks, July-Dec., First National Bank of Washington, 025339 1, School, 1970 (Box 203, Folder 1988)
  - Bank Checks, Aug., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1970 (Box 203, Folder 1989)
  - Bank Checks, Oct., First National Bank of Washington, 0252565, Subscriptions, 1970 (Box 203, Folder 1990)
  - Bank Checks, Oct., Union Trust, 3 057 860, Payroll, 1970 (Box 203, Folder 1991)
  - Bank Checks, Nov., First National Bank of Washington, 0252565, Subscriptions, 1970 (Box 204, Folder 1992)
  - Bank Checks, Dec., First National Bank of Washington, 0252565, Subscriptions, 1970 (Box 204, Folder 1993)
  - Bank Checks, First National Bank of Washington, 025 2492, Educational Grant, 1970-1971 (Box 204, Folder 1994)
  - Bank Checks, Jan.-Feb., First National Bank of Washington,-25256 5, Sub-, 1971 (Box 204, Folder 1995)
  - Bank Checks, Jan.-Apr., First National Bank of Washington, 025339 1, School, 1971 (Box 205, Folder 1996)
  - Bank Checks, Feb.-Mar., National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, 1971 (Box 205, Folder 1997)
  - Bank Checks, Mar.-Apr., First National Bank of Washington, 025 256 5, 1971 (Box 205, Folder 1998)
  - Bank Checks, Apr.-May, National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, 1971 (Box 206, Folder 1999)
  - Bank Checks, May-June, First National Bank of Washington, 025 256 5, 1971 (Box 206, Folder 2000)
  - Bank Checks, May-June, First National Bank of Washington, 025 848 2, Subscriptions, 1971 (Box 206, Folder 2001)
  - Bank Checks, May-Aug., First National Bank of Washington, 025 339 1, School, 1971 (Box 206, Folder 2002)
  - Bank Checks, May-Dec., Suburban Trust Company, 54 208 4, 1971 (Box 207, Folder 2003)
  - Bank Checks, June-July, National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, 1971 (Box 207, Folder 2004)
  - Bank Checks, July-Aug., First National Bank of Washington, 025 256 5, 1971 (Box 207, Folder 2005)
  - Bank Checks, July-Sept., First National Bank of Washington, 025 848 2, Subscriptions, 1971 (Box 207, Folder 2006)
  - Bank Checks, Aug., National Bank of Washington, 048 44 9, 1971 (Box 208, Folder 2007)
  - Bank Checks, Sept., First National Bank of Washington, 025 256 5, 1971 (Box 208, Folder 2008)
  - Bank Checks, Sept.-Dec., First National Bank of Washington, 025 339 1, School, 1971 (Box 208, Folder 2009)
  - Bank Checks, Oct., First National Bank of Washington, 025 256 5, 1971 (Box 208, Folder 2010)
  - Bank Checks, Oct.-Nov., First National Bank of Washington, 025 848 2, Subscriptions, 1971 (Box 208, Folder 2011)
  - Bank Checks, Nov.-Dec., First National Bank of Washington, 025 256 5, 1971 (Box 209, Folder 2012)
  - Bank Checks, Dec., First National Bank of Washington, 025 848 2, Subscriptions, 1971 (Box 209, Folder 2013)
  - Bank Checks, Union Trust, 3 057 860, 1971 (Box 209, Folder 2014)
  - Bank Checks, Jan.-Feb., First National Bank, 025 848 2, Subscriptions, 1972 (Box 209, Folder 2015)
  - Bank Checks, Jan.-Feb., First National Bank, 025 848 2, Subscriptions, 1972 (Box 209, Folder 2016)
  - Bank Checks, Jan.-Apr., First National Bank, 025 339 1, School, 1972 (Box 210, Folder 2017)
  - Bank Checks, Mar., First National Bank, 025 256 5, 1972 (Box 210, Folder 2018)
  - Bank Checks, Mar.-Apr., First National Bank, 025 848 2, Subscriptions, 1972 (Box 210, Folder 2019)
  - Bank Checks, Apr., First National Bank, 025 256 5, 1972 (Box 211, Folder 2020)
  - Bank Checks, Apr.-May, First National Bank, 026 691 4, Subscriptions, 1972 (Box 211, Folder 2021)
  - Bank Checks, May, First National Bank, 025 848 2, Subscriptions, 1972 (Box 211, Folder 2022)
  - Bank Checks, May-July, First National Bank, 025 256 5, 1972 (Box 211, Folder 2023)
  - Bank Checks, May-July, First National Bank, 0253395 1, School, 1972 (Box 212, Folder 2024)
  - Bank Checks, June, First National Bank, 025 848 2, Subscriptions, 1972 (Box 212, Folder 2025)
  - Bank Checks, July, First National Bank, 026 691 4, Subscriptions, 1972 (Box 212, Folder 2026)
  - Bank Checks, July-Jan.1973, First National Bank, 025 848 2, Subcriptions, 1972 (Box 212, Folder 2027)
  - Bank Checks, Aug.-Sept., First National Bank,025256 5, 1972 (Box 213, Folder 2028)